Hello friends, I welcome you to the
YouTube channel Mantra Group. Today we
will talk about how to buy a helpline.
What things should we keep in mind while taking a health policy
and what should be done.
First of all, let's compare
which company's product is less expensive. Along with this,
I will tell you what things you should pay attention to.
But friends, what is most important for a friend is
his tension. Should
you take a family floater or dinner
polythene in the name of Jabardast or should you
take some such features that you can get a job?
We will talk about all these things
in a good video. We will see
how much payment should be made
and that it is applied on the best quality.
We have
function fruits available for policy complaint.
Friends, whenever we buy a handsfree,
we should keep these things in mind. Keep
noting the above points. Compare the health. If you
keep these things in mind, then
whatever hairstyle you buy, it
proves to be more beneficial for the peace of mind. Like,
which company comes first,
you should choose. You should select the company when the
combined  About the company you will get history
first like our channel Opportunities all the
companies sell so that their Renu
Vimleshwar city some companies give priority,
Ignore friend, you are liking
that time efficient you get violent I am this
facility war profit and there
you can get treatment quickly without depositing any money
friend joke till 5 days camp office
whatever matters friends when we go to any
doctor's nearby to
ensure then
we see that
at the hospital counter there is a TPA guy running battery
war this question is
sitting at the hospital counter who
processes the slam for this you have to
show your hunting house card, it is decided to find a
child for two days, it solves the problem,
I will tell you the things which you should keep in mind in the policy like this,
you will keep using the
plane process, make this much pass, this is the first thing
you should keep in mind
how many villages located on the container network are
buying this ever slam version from that company  You should check how many network hospitals they have,
so see if there is one
near you or not, if the rules of the office are there or
not, then it is from that company's
policy that you should take time, as you
know now, one thing is that if you do
not fall ill first, then you will not have to worry about it for those days, then you will
not have to take some steps, so before and after this, the
medical test is covered for the past few days, that is
not doing polythene,
hello friends, good night, while talking about input,
you should pay attention, it may be worth it or
not, you should pay attention, you
get no claim bonus, I
think you should get
free medical checkup with the company, whether you are getting free
medical checkup or not, then the
company gives it in a year or two years, which
depends on your health related, whether
you are systematic like this, then
you should get medical test, along with this, the ideal
cover, how much have you taken your time code, what is the
teacher in the policy,
what is final in it, as of today's date,
giving a policy below 5 lakhs  There is no pimple, I will tell
you family floater volunteers and you
collect some points a week ago, there would have been
some such illness during day care pass duty,
hence hospitalization is
not necessary, you know friends medical
insurance mediclaim works well then it is
24th of modernization, if there were
no suicide missions at printer worship place
then you do not get medical money,
but take the interest of contractor, there is such a thing,
coat paint is being national station, now
you get our money, when an
accident is asked, you have to
buy retail pack, when you have to get an
operation done, it is a 24 hour operation, then
you get updates in that and also
get some cashback, in some companies you
will see that for whatever days you have notification,
your interruptions stop, so the
company on its side, after watching some test match and
typing it, says income, expenses get stopped only after typing,
during our poster making, the company keeps
thinking about income, what is your
timing, so all these fati side sensitive
in your Modi ji medical, apart from this
friends I want to tell you  I would like to say one more thing
that you should use 40% of the individual maximum,
friend, how much investment should be made, I cannot
say friends,
if it is possible for you, then
you should take an individual pass, if your mother and father are yours, then a
policy is
made for them and you have to take separate policies because the
premium of the policy is 1529, the
most popular one, you know that heart
developing more apps, whichever mountain
insurance works, then
in health insurance you need timing Roshan
for your family, if you are
married or not, you will have to take Bengali
and if you have a criminal, then
make an updated policy for them so that as the number
of apps increases, they can
become more shiny
and teams like North Africa, it is
not a load on the whole family, so when you
go for this product, keep these people in
mind, apart from these, you should
click on the company, you can also do
medical positive, whenever you buy,
see that its time cannot be passed,
behind it group - need task to help  Does it work or
not, how is the customer care,
now we will take care of all these things, then according to
my knowledge, you are right, I have
settled in written buy, I have
put it on for the committee, not for distraction, if you
need money, you can go there and return the caffeine suggestion,
Yadav Bhai, there is a pendant near the hands that gives
you good sleep, we file the apk,
all these companies are estate companies,
good companies, Amitabh Prem Aasthaan is very
good, now he will remain the minister, the PM of your place, you
can complain about that, you will find it
in the description,
hello friends, that's all for today,
in the next video we are going to include Karan show.